What's interesting about October of 2019
and August of 2026? Well, what's
interesting is that this is this was an
apathetic top. Okay, it was an apathetic
top. No rotation to altcoins. QT had
just ended and it's it was the first
rally above the 200 day moving average.
Now, if you're having a hard time sort
of buying into this idea, the thing to
consider is if the uptrend can take
longer than the 2019 uptrend, why can't
the downtrend take a little bit longer
than the 2019 downtrend? And so, if you
think about it through that lens, this
is the first rally above the 200 day
moving average after falling below it
after an apathetic top. And again,
Bitcoin rallied about 17 to 18% above
the 200 day moving average. Let's go see
where we are now. And then we're going
to get into your favorite part of this
video, which will be the news that
accompanied both rallies.